["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
[footsteps approaching]
- Now then, time to get
today's work started.
Hmm?
What, Zabuton?
A bee?
It's huge.
What will you do with it?
Are you going to eat it?
So then you'll keep it as a pet?
Yeah, it might be dangerous.
Oh, it won't fight back anymore?
Okay, got it.
There we go.
I built a little house for the
bee's nest near the orchard.
They built a big nest inside
in about 10 days.
The worker bees are all busy
taking care of their jobs.
By the way, only the queen
is that big.
The worker bees are all
normal-sized.
If I leave them here like this,
I wonder if they'll make honey
that I can harvest.
The crops in the field
have flowering plants,
but maybe I should plant
a flower garden nearby
if I wanna harvest honey.
- Hello?
Hiraku?
[Tia screaming]
Pardon the intrusion!
- Maybe she's been stung
before or something.
[hammer tapping]
[Hiraku grunting]
[Hiraku sighing]
- What's this?
- Reservoir.
Or at least it will be one day.
I planned on drawing water
from the river
through a waterway,
and I've been busy with
other stuff lately.
- I see, then.
How far have you progressed
with the waterway construction?
- Not even far enough to decide
what I'm going to
make out of it yet.
There's actually
quite a bit of distance
between here and the river.
- [Lea] First we need to decide
what to build it out of.
- [Hiraku] Let's see.
I've always pictured waterways
as built from stone.
- [Lea] Hm.
I think it would be a bit
difficult to find stone
to work with around here.
- Then should we use wood?
- Well, we certainly do have
a lot of wood here,
but if we have a long waterway,
the gaps in the wood will
cause quite a bit of leakage.
- Hm.
[water dripping]
In that case, we'll use this.
[hammer thumping]
A compacted dirt,
using the almighty tool.
It's about as hard as concrete.
This should work great.
- As what?
- Oh, never mind.
I actually had a mountain
of dirt left over
from digging out the reservoir
that I wasn't sure
what to do with.
We went right into
mass production mode.
- [All] One! Two! One!
- [Hiraku] Next!
We built an intake gate
for the water
at the top of the waterfall,
then built up the
foundation using dirt,
and placed parts of the
waterway on top of it.
- [Lea] Okay. A little
more this way.
[Lea grunting]
[Leezay humming]
- [Hiraku] I let
the elves handle
the basic foundation work.
- Good work.
- Good work!
- [Hiraku] I focused on
sealing the seams
and strengthening
the foundation.
Thanks to all of
their hard work,
the construction moved along
a lot faster than
I was expecting.
[water rushing]
[water splashing]
[Lea laughing]
Now we won't have to climb
in and out of the well
for water every day.
- Yeah!
This should make watering
the crops easier, too.
[fish flapping]
- Oh, look at this.
I haven't been able
to catch any,
but now that we have
access to the river,
I can finally eat fish.
I just need to decide how
I'm going to prepare them.
You know, the rabbits in this
forest may be really vicious,
but the fish here seem
to be pretty normal.
I'm really glad that
they're so easy to-
[fish thudding]
[Hiraku screaming]
[blade ringing]
- Oh!
[wood rattling]
[fire crackling]
- [Lu] Aren't those fish from
the forest of death waters?
- Yeah.
Those are the really
vicious ones, too.
- I wonder if it's
safe to eat those.
[all humming]
[triumphant chord playing]
- Here you go.
Just for you.
- Oh no. [laughing]
You should eat first.
You made it.
- Yeah, she's right.
You're the one who made it.
- Are you sure?
Then I'll help myself.
[relaxed music playing]
[Hiraku chewing]
It looks and tastes
just like salmon!
- Like ham?
- [Hiraku] Uh, forget
what I said.
Here, don't be shy.
[both gasping]
Eat up.
[both whimpering]
[Lu gulping]
- This is...
- So...
So delicious!
[all murmuring]
- So would you all
like to try some?
- [All] Mhm!
- [Hiraku] They all loved it,
so we quickly
went through it all.
But after that, we caught more
and preserved it with salt
so we could store them.
[relaxed music ending]
I decided to try
tilling with the hoe
while thinking about
rice plants,
and rice plants popped up.
I didn't know that they
could grow in normal soil
but now that we have the
waterways built here...
[drum banging]
We're building a rice paddy.
- Did you say a paddy?
[hoe swiping]
[Hiraku grunting]
[grand music beginning]
[elves humming]
- Huh?
- It looks just like a
normal crop field, though.
- [Hiraku] I'm just
getting started here.
[wood rattling]
[water rushing]
[elves gasping]
- Oh!
- [Lea] Are you building
a pond too?
Oh, I know what it's!
You're going to keep
fish here, right?
- [laughing] I guess
that's how it looks.
Now, I'm going to need
you all to help me
with this next part.
- What? What should we do?
[water splashing]
It's all slimy.
[Lea whining]
[elves murmuring]
- Okay, everyone, let's plant
all these seedlings.
- Ah!
[Lees grunting]
[Leef and Leely laughing]
The girls were a little
nervous at first,
but they got the hang of it.
The rice planting went off
without a hitch.
I put Zabuton's children
in charge
of keeping pests
out of the area.
I'm not sure if it was
thanks to the water
or the almighty farming tool,
[elves cheering]
but the rice plants
grew much faster
than I expected them to.
And now, it's time to harvest.
I had Lea and the girls
help me with this too,
[blades ringing]
[elves grunting]
and thanks to them, it was done
in the blink of an eye.
[relaxed music]
- [Lea] So what exactly
are we doing?
- We're drying them so we can
get all the moisture out.
- Huh?
You know about all kinds of
interesting things, don't you?
- [laughs] I just
happened upon this.
That's right.
I just happened to watch an idol
doing this on TV one time.
- [Lu] Hmm.
So these are the crops
you grew in that paddy, then?
- What are you going
to do with them now?
- We'll thresh them.
- You'll thresh them?
- Yep.
- Ah.
- Let's see...
I'm pretty sure the old
thresher I saw in a museum
looks something like this.
[Hiraku grunting]
[plants rustling]
[girls applauding]
[laughing] That's
the gist of it.
[rice shuffling]
Next, we put them
through a sieve
to get rid of any remaining
leaves or plant matter.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- [Hiraku] Then we
use a mortar
to remove the husk
from the rice,
and now we use a pestle
to polish the rice.
[Lecott sighing]
[pestle thumping]
- This stuff really
takes a lot of work.
- Yeah.
Can you not eat it
if you don't go through
all these steps?
[rice glittering]
[Hiraku sighing]
- Are you finally finished?
- Yeah.
- So that means we can
eat it now, doesn't it?
- No, not yet.
[Lu groaning]
[Tia gasping]
[gentle music playing]
- What happens now?
- I'm cooking the rice.
If I remember the way to
cook rice in a kettle
first you start it nice and
slow, and then once it rises
cut the heat and simmer,
add a fist full of straw
to the fire.
Then no matter what happens,
don't lift the lid.
- Was that a spell?
- Don't know.
I've never heard it before.
- [Hiraku] Hey, Lu?
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- [Hiraku] Could you use
your magic to light the fire?
- [Lu] Sure, I'd be happy to.
It's finally time
for the great sage
Lord Lulucy to show
what she can do.
I'll blast you one and all
into smithereens!
- Uh... It's supposed to be
slow, so a low flame.
- Aw, come on.
How incredibly boring.
[fire roaring]
I wonder what kind of food
he's making this time.
- [Tia] I'm not sure
what he's making,
but I'm curious to see
what the spell did.
[Lecott gulping]
[lid rattling]
[chimes tinkling]
- [Hiraku] Oh!
It came out perfect.
- It's done now, right?
- Not yet.
[Lu grunting]
- [All] Oh!
[Hiraku grunting]
[rice sparkling]
- This thing here is what he
spent all that time making?
- [Hiraku] Yeah.
If you're going to try rice,
then I think rice balls
are the way to go.
- Well, after you then.
[Lu gasping]
- Fine, I'll do it.
[Lu inhaling]
[Lu chewing]
Mm!
Mhm!
[whimsical music playing]
- Ah?
[Tia chewing]
Mm!
It's delicious.
- Glad to hear.
- Wait a sec.
This is the fish
from the other day!
- [Hiraku] Yeah, the saltiness
goes with the rice.
- Mm.
Now I feel like all that
hard work was worth it.
- Mhm.
This is my happiest moment
as a farmer here yet.
Huh?
Are they good?
- [All] Mhm!
- Well, it looks
like they're a hit.
I'll just have to work
harder and make more.
[Hiraku chewing]
Next time, I think I'll do
a different filling.
[delicate music playing]
[leaves rustling]
[water sloshing]
[Hiraku sighing]
We should stop here for today.
- Okay.
[rustic music beginning]
[light ringing]
[Lea humming]
[Leely grunting]
[light ringing]
[Leef and Leezay humming]
[water splashing]
[light ringing]
[Lees and Leeta giggling]
[both gasping]
[Lecott groaning]
[Lecott sneezing]
[light ringing]
[Lecott sniffling]
- Apparently they can all clean
themselves off with magic.
It's times like this
I really wish
I had a bath I could hop in.
Well, I did build a waterway,
so I'll give it a shot.
- You're building a bath?
- Yeah.
- What's a bath, exactly?
- It's a place where you wash
your body with warm water.
A furnace to heat up the water,
a tub to hold the water,
a place to wash your body.
I wanna put a changing room
in there too.
- Huh?
- [Lea] Can't we just
wash ourselves
in a river or something?
- [Hiraku] Isn't it too cold
during the winter?
- [Lea] Yeah, I guess
you're right.
- Just trust me!
Baths are great!
I want to build one,
no matter what it takes.
It's good for your circulation.
- [Lea] We'll help you build it.
[bright music playing]
- [Hiraku] And so construction
began right away.
The furnace was made
from blocks of dirt
compacted with the hammer.
- Oh!
- [Hiraku] We fed it water
brought in from the waterway,
and the most important
part of the bath,
the tub itself.
[Lea giggling]
I wanna make it
as big as possible.
We made stools to sit on
in the washing area.
- It seems to be going well.
- Hm.
- What is it?
- I'm just now noticing this.
Pulling water from the
river is fine and all,
but is it okay to put
our wastewater
back into the river
from our bath?
- [Tia] If that's what
you're worried about,
we can just use slimes.
- Some slimes?
- Yeah.
They eat waste and dead
organic matter and purify it.
They're nature's
cleaning machines.
- Aren't those
weak-looking monsters,
that are actually really
dangerous and end up being
the number one cause of
death in new adventurers?
[soul moaning]
[game beeping]
- That's not how it is at all.
I'll go catch some!
All done.
[slime bouncing]
- She grabbed them from
near the earlier village.
[Kuro panting]
Will you eat this?
Okay, got it.
[slimes plopping]
I built a purification
pool for the slimes
in the waste waterway.
- If we put slimes
in the toilet,
they'll clean everything
nasty in there for us.
- I'm glad they'll do that,
but I don't know if I have
the courage to do my business
right above a slime's head.
And just like that, the
wastewater problem was solved.
Now I just need to
grab some firewood
and the bath will be
ready to go.
Hm?
A mushroom.
I've actually been
too afraid to eat
any of the mushrooms
in this forest,
'cause I didn't know which
ones might be poisonous.
- You made the right choice.
Things like this are
really hard to tell apart.
- They're pretty incredible
if you cook them thoroughly.
- If you'd like me to, I'd be
happy to eliminate them.
- [Hiraku] Huh? Is that
what we're talking about?
The residents all had
different opinions.
[light humming]
In that case,
Shiitake, shiitake, shimeji...
[hammer thumping]
I went to hurry up and grow
all the mushrooms I knew.
I'm not sure if this was
the right way to do it.
Shiitake again.
I completely forgot
about the bath.
Ah.
Now I'm going to teach you
how to use the bath.
Take your clothes off
in the changing room.
However, before you
get into the tub-
- Ah?
- [Hiraku] You first
need to rinse
and lightly wash yourself off
in the washing area.
- [Lea] Um, excuse me.
- Hm?
- It would be very helpful
if you could demonstrate.
- You want me to show you?
[cloth rustling]
- Uh...
First you get undressed,
[water splashing]
[elves humming]
then you rinse yourself,
then you wash yourself.
Finally, get into
the bath and...
Ah, it's the best.
- [All] Ah.
Oh?
- I can really feel it.
How long has it been
since I bathed like this?
I wasn't allowed to
get into a bath
while I was hospitalized.
Huh? Zoned out.
So anyways, that's how
you enjoy it...
- [All] Okay!
[lively music beginning]
[elves giggling]
- It's nice to be able to relax
and wash ourselves like this.
- Uh, sorry.
- Hm?
- [Hiraku] No, it's just that...
I'll get out first.
You all can just take your time.
- [Lu] Why is that?
Can't we all just
bathe together?
- [Tia] Yeah, She's right.
This way we don't need to
heat up the water again.
- Well, yeah,
you're right about that.
But still, I...
[water bubbling]
I'm too embarrassed to relax
with them all around
me right now.
In the end, there wasn't
much time for me to relax
while in the bath.
I should have built
a separate men's bath.
- [Lu] Wouldn't that just be
a private bath for you?
- [Tia] No fair, you can't
have a bath for just you.
- [Hiraku] Is that what
you guys think?
[wind rustling]
[footsteps approaching]
Hm?
[Hiraku laughing]
Looks like it worked.
Maybe I'll make a
mushroom hotpot tonight.
[dog barking]
What?
The dogs found five
new elves in the forest
and brought them here.
- I'm Lafa.
- I'm Lassa.
- I'm Lalasha.
- I'm Lalu.
- I'm Lami.
?- [Hiraku] You're all "La?"
- Oh, you mean our
names are "La."
The reason our names are...
- [Hiraku] You're all
related, right?
- That's right.
You already knew that?
- [Hiraku] Do they all
want to live here too?
- They do.
They used to live in the
same village as all of us.
- Since we left,
we've been living our lives
as mere wanderers.
It's been 200 years since
we've seen them.
- 200?
You must have had
a really rough time.
It's fine by me.
[Lafa gasping]
If you'd like,
you can live with us.
- [All] Thank you very much.
- All right, let's start
building you all
a house to live in.
I know. Why don't we
take this time
to make some improvements
to your house?
- Hm?
Well, there are more people.
I guess it's getting
kind of cramped.
- We'll help you with
the work, so don't worry.
- Oh, thank you.
That's helpful.
- Okay, everyone, let's get
started on today's work.
- [All] Okay.
[all giggling]
And to ensure the
revival of our race,
let's start making children.
- [All] Yeah!
[elves giggling]
- I'm not sure how they
intended to make children,
but it's nice to see
they're so optimistic.
- Let's start now!
- What?
- [Lea] It's time to
make houses.
- [Hiraku] [stammering]
Yeah, let's go!
Farming Life...
- [Tia] in Another...
- [Hiraku] World.
- Let's start making children.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
[elves giggling]
- [Kuro] It appears
the number of females
in my master's pack has
increased again.
[Kuro growling]
My name is Kuro.
Before I met my master, I didn't
have a name to call my own.
[nostalgic music beginning]
Starting from the moment
I was born,
I spent my whole life
in this forest alone.
[footprints approaching]
I never lost a single fight
to another male.
I planned on living
my whole life
doing whatever I pleased, and
hunting when I needed to eat.
But one day, I met a female.
[chime ringing]
I didn't stand a chance
against her.
After my complete loss
to that female,
we began to travel together.
Sometime after that,
her belly started to grow,
and soon she gave birth
to our children.
There are animals in this
forest who lead around
packs of their little ones.
When I thought about how that
would become my life one day,
it didn't seem so bad.
But then, our luck
took a turn for worse.
[wolf whining]
We ran into the one they
call the grappler bear,
the king of this forest.
I don't know if he decided
on a whim to spare us,
or if he was just full,
but he didn't eat us.
We were still gravely injured,
and as a result,
we couldn't hunt for food.
We'd become so weak that our
former prey had driven us away.
We found ourselves at
the center of this forest,
a place where even the grappler
bear doesn't dare to tread.
[footsteps approaching]
[Hiraku humming]
What we did find there
was a human male.
- Hm?
- [Kuro] I always thought that
people living in the forest
kept themselves hidden,
and never stayed in
one place for too long.
How could someone
so obviously weak-looking
survive here all by himself?
It was that.
I felt a limitless power
coming from that tool.
We thought our lives
were over,
and we'd already made
our peace with that.
- Hm.
[wolves chewing]
- [Kuro] But he shared
his prey with us.
He took care of us.
[lighthearted music playing]
This is the meat of a gate boar.
I'm impressed that he was able
to hunt such a great beast.
We don't have any desire
to fight him.
The female and I have
decided that this male
will be our master.
Our master gave us names,
as well as a home to live in.
The meat he cleans for us
and the vegetables
he cooks are delicious.
But the most delicious part
of an animal is the innards.
Throwing that away
is a terrible waste.
Before long, our children grew
up and our family got bigger.
Our master also became
the leader
of a large pack of his own.
Looking at all the
females he leads,
I can't help but think
that he must be more
than just a weak human,
as I once thought he was.
My only concern now
is our master doesn't
seem to understand.
He's unaware that we are
the terrifying monsters
known as the inferno wolves.
Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
[Kuro barking]
Right now,
I'm just thankful that my good
fortune led me here to him.
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
[rustic music playing]